Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/jordan9smith (LinkedIn) www.theplaybookproject.com (Company)

Top Skills

Cross-functional Collaborations
Creative Problem Solving
Sales Enablement

Languages

Spanish (Full Professional)

Q'eqchi' (Limited Working)

English (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Basic Adult/Child/Infant First Aid NFHS Coaching Fundamentals, Concussion, Sexual Abuse, and Hazing/Bullying Training

1st Place Team - MBA Capstone Marketplace Simulation

Product Management: Building a Product Roadmap

Sales Enablement

Honors-Awards

Eagle Scout

2017 5A State Champion - Lehi Football

2022 6A State Champion - Skyridge Football

Jordan Smith

Recent MBA Grad

Lehi, Utah, United States

Summary

An analytical and meticulous working professional known for exemplary team-building and project oversight skills. Gifted at working with all types of personalities. Performance history of developing strong collaborative relationships and delivering impressive results.

Top sales performer with 7 years of experience in D2D, Retail, and SaaS

3 years as a high school educator teaching financial literacy with concurrent enrollment, marketing, sports marketing, and retailing.

11 years of coaching experience with positions held of Youth Football Offensive Assistant, Sophomore Position Coach, Sophomore Defensive Coordinator, Sophomore Offensive Coordinator, Sophomore Head Coach, JV Offensive Coordinator, Varsity Position Coach, Varsity Offensive Advisor, Varsity Pass Game Coordinator, and Varsity Offensive Coordinator.

Two-Time State Champion Coach - 2017 5A Lehi HS and 2022 6A Skyridge HS

I have had the opportunity to help multiple players on their journey to play football at the collegiate level including 24 FBS, 14 FCS, and 26 DII/DIII/NAIA/NJCAA players.

Assisted at Level Up Elite and Polynesian Bowl Football Camps

Experience

Stay at Home Parent
Assistant Chief Executive Director of Children Development
July 2023 - Present (10 months)

Particl

11 months

Enterprise BDR & Revenue Enablement June 2023 - June 2023 (1 month)

Salt Lake City, Utah, United States

Cold outreach to brands with \$500m+ of revenue

#1 SDR for Demos Set and Held since start date #2 SDR for most business won since start date

*Leveraged newly developed messaging to reach out to large, well-known brands

*Skilled in Salesforce, Outreach.io, ZoomInfo, Clearbit, Seamless.ai, Notion, Slack, Zoom, Pitch, Loom, and G Suite

Mid-Market BDR & Revenue Enablement January 2023 - May 2023 (5 months) Salt Lake City Metropolitan Area

Cold outreach to retail brands with \$51m+ of revenue

- *Created new messaging resulting in a 2x increase in email opens
- *Created new email deliverability strategy that cut bounce rates in half
- *Created new ICP matrix and outbound strategy
- *Consistently worked cross-functionally with customer success and marketing to develop proper outreach strategies and to better define the ICP and buyer personas

SMB BDR

August 2022 - December 2022 (5 months)

Salt Lake City Metropolitan Area

Attained 242% Quota in the first 90 Days

Cold outreach to retail brands up to \$50m of revenue

Alpine School District
Financial Literacy & Business Teacher
March 2019 - July 2022 (3 years 5 months)
Eagle Mountain, Utah, United States

Cedar Valley High School 2020-2022 School Years Courses Taught: Financial Literacy with Concurrent Enrollment and added Digital/Online Curriculum

2019-2020 School Year Courses Taught:

Financial Literacy with Concurrent Enrollment

Marketing, Sports Marketing, Retailing (100% State CTE State Test Pass Rate in Retailing)

Nike

Sales Associate

October 2015 - March 2019 (3 years 6 months)

Lehi, Utah

- *Worked at the Nike Factory Outlet retail store
- *Worked on the sales floor helping customers make informed decisions in the footwear department
- *Helped customers complete purchases at the cash register
- *Upsold customers according to their interests and needs

Kelly Services Substitute Teacher August 2014 - May 2015 (10 months)

Alpine School District

- *Executed daily lesson plans for classes from 1st-12th grade
- *Substituted for full Spanish immersion classes weekly

DISH Network

1 year 4 months

Regional Sales Manager

September 2013 - August 2014 (1 year)

- *Recruited and trained 17 new sales representatives
- *Managed territories for all reps within the Bay Area (San Jose, San Francisco, and Oakland)
- *Door-to-door sales and side-by-side training
- *Conduct daily meetings and motivate local team members as well as weekly meeting with the larger area as a whole

Independent Sales Representative

May 2013 - September 2013 (5 months)

Pittsburg, California

- *Full-time door-to-door sales
- *Personal time management

- *Daily client based work
- *Organized and scheduled my own appointments
- *Coordinated with technicians to ensure timely installation

ADT

Customer Support Representative

May 2012 - February 2013 (10 months)

Orem, Utah, United States

- *Scheduled installations for ADT Security Systems through Authorized Retailer
- Elite Security
- *Onboarding for new customers upon installation
- *Inbound customer service calls including basic tech support

Western Community Bank (Acquired by Community Bancorp in 2010)

Bank Teller

June 2009 - January 2010 (8 months)

Orem, Utah, United States

- *Stay up to date on current compliance laws
- *Complete withdrawal and deposit transactions
- *Participated in regular vault cash audits
- *Managed personal cash-on-hand availability and daily transaction recordkeeping

Education

Western Governors University

Master of Business Administration - MBA · (January 2021 - May 2023)

Grand Canyon University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Applied Business Management · (September 2017 - April 2019)

Utah Valley University

Associate's Degree, General Studies · (September 2014 - December 2016)

Brigham Young University

General Studies · (September 2012 - December 2013)

Brigham Young University

General Studies · (September 2009 - December 2009)

Activity

04/18/2024, Imeila Fonua added candidate to BDR- Test Sample

Page 5 of 5